-brandon driesse

Animator - Game Developer

brandon.driesse@gmail.com



Profile

Lover of cartoons and vocal supporter of independent animation and games on the internet through sites like Newgrounds.com. Five years making video games, three years of freelance animating, and twenty or so years of starved passion to create. Hobbies range from tennis to building computers to stop-motion films to photogrammetry to running audio capture on commercial film shoots.

I make stuff; sometimes for money, but always for fun.

Experience

Experience	
2015 - Present	Creative Director - Scarecrow Arts Independent Game Developer/Publisher Video Production, Motion Graphics, and Developer of Freeware Tools/Scripts for Adobe After Effects
2015 - 2020	The Story Goes On (Steam, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch) Initial Release: March 2nd 2018 RE-RELEASED: March 2nd 2020
2018	Newgrounds Summer Animation Jam Third Place Winner - Overall Four Animations Completed in Six Weeks
2015	Intern - Roman Media Group LLC Database Organization and Vectorizing Company Assets
2014	SkillsUSA Second Place Medalist in the Category of Digital Design
2013 - 2018	Paige - Lincoln Park Public Library Minor Building Maintenance, Light Installation, IT Support, Website Management, and Federal Tax Document Filing

Education

2018- Present	Savannah College of Art and Design Junior Year working toward Animation BFA
2015 - 2018	County College of Morris A.A.S. Digital Media Technology
2011 - 2015	Morris County School of Technology Academy of Digital Design